the versatility of dumbbells is
unmatched and if you're anything like me
a good pair of dumbbells are your best
friend in the gym but when you're
talking about a good pair of dumbbells
you have to mention rogue available in
both pairs and sets these bad boys range
from two and a half all the way up to
125 pounds they feature an ergonomic
handle that's chrome plated and a knurl
that's ideal for high ref exercises
what's up everybody it's jake back in
the barbie garage gym and for today's
review i've got a pair of rogue
dumbbells for you guys in this video i'm
going to walk you through everything
these dumbbells have to offer the
features the price some pros and cons
and who should or should not add these
to their home gym
but before we get started gotta let you
know we have reviewed a lot of dumbbells
on barbin.com if you want to find out
more about our top picks just google
barbin best dumbbells and you can read
all about it let's get to it
okay so what do i like about these
dumbbells well for starters they're
coming from rogue which is a high
quality brand it's no exception here
with these dumbbells they're of high
quality and they're going to last you a
really long time
since they are in that hexagon shape it
makes them great for using them on the
floor for any type of push-up variations
and plus they're not going to roll away
from you too far if you drop them since
the hexagon heads are coated in rubber
it makes them ideal for at-home usage
meaning they're not going to tear up
your floors if you drop them over time
the ergonomic handle here feels really
good in your hands and plus the knurling
is on the medium side of things so it's
not going to tear up your hands with
those high rep movements you often use
with dumbbells and plus you can get them
in both pairs or as a full set
now what about those potential cons that
could happen with these dumbbells
while they're not really considered on
the expensive side of things compared to
the market there's definitely cheaper
dumbbells out there for you to buy so if
you're on a really tight budget you
might not want to consider these maybe
consider one of those cheaper options
but those probably are not of high
quality like these are right here
and not everybody has enough room for a
full set of dumbbells
if you're one of those people who
doesn't have enough room
i would suggest going with an adjustable
pair of dumbbells there's a lot of solid
adjustable dumbbells out there for you
to purchase
so let's talk about money now and how
much you'll be looking at spending with
the individual pairs that two and a half
pound pairs me about 20 bucks the 25
pound pair you see here today that's
about 90 and that 125 pound pair that's
about 450 bucks
the sets are gonna feature five pound
intervals and those are going to be
priced as follows now that five to fifty
pound set it's about a thousand dollars
the 55 to 100 pound set it's about
twenty nine hundred dollars in the 105
to 125 pound set
that's about twenty two hundred dollars
now this really isn't that bad once you
consider the high quality you're gonna
get with these dumbbells the biggest
downside though
is if you want your dumbbells to range
from five to a hundred pounds
if that's the case you're gonna have to
get the 5 to 50 pound set
and the 55 to 100 pound set which really
will wind up costing you more money than
say if you went for the 500 pound set
from rep fitness
but if you have the budget just buy
these dumbbells in that full set i think
you'll be really happy
they're tough as nails meaning they're
gonna be around for a long time they
feel good in your hands
and plus they look good
okay so let's dig into the build now
with these rogue dumbbells you'll notice
anything 10 pounds in less is gonna have
a handle diameter of 25 millimeters once
you get to 12 and a half and up
well that diameter is going to jump up
to 35 millimeters per handle now the
handles are ergonomically shaped and if
you don't know what that means basically
they're thicker in the middle than they
are at the ends the handles are also
chrome plated and they have a nice
medium
knurling which is not going to tear up
your hands while also giving you a good
grip during your lifts
i personally really like the hexagon
shaped heads i like using them for
push-ups they're going to put my wrist
in a more natural position
plus i can drop them and not have to run
across the gym chasing them down
now
as far as construction goes i tried to
reach out to rogue because they're
listed as proprietary head to handle
construction
they weren't able to give me a good
answer on that but just know that with
these dumbbells they're really good
quality rogue is known for their high
quality products no exception with these
dumbbells
i really am not worried whatsoever while
using them i can drop them and not not
be scared they're gonna break on me and
while the numbering on the heads are the
exact same color as the rest of the
rubber
you don't have to worry about not
knowing which dumbbell is which because
there is a little bit of a lip right
here meaning they pop out at you
okay so who should purchase these rogue
dumbbells well anybody out there looking
for a pair of high quality dumbbells
with a rubber coating you're going to be
happy with this product here it's going
to protect the dumbbell itself but also
prevent your floors from any potential
damage as well
since they do have this hexagon shaped
head they're great for somebody like
myself who wants to use their dumbbells
for different push-up variations
and since you can purchase these in
individual pairs you know you can go and
get a pair at a time until you have that
full set that you're looking for okay so
what about the people that might not
want to have these dumbbells on their
radar
well look trust me i know how much fun
it is to go and get the big name brands
but don't break the bank if you can't
afford these dumbbells there's cheaper
options out there for you and i promise
you're gonna get just as strong with
those other brands
now not everybody has enough space for
dumbbells to be lying around or maybe
for a full set with a rack so if you're
one of those people i would definitely
consider getting a pair of adjustable
dumbbells like i said there's a lot of
really good options for you to go and
purchase
and this last point is really just
personal preference here if you want
your dumbbells to have a fully knurled
handle
you know these don't have that so if
that's something that you want i would
definitely suggest looking for another
option because there are brands out
there that do feature a fully knurled
handle
that's all i have for you guys today on
the rogue hex dumbbells
this is a really nice option to consider
when you're looking to fill out your
home gym i personally love the hexagon
shaped head they're going to allow me to
do some superset push-ups
in my workout routine
plus it's really nice knowing that if i
drop them they're not going to roll all
the way across the room and make me go
chase after them
rogue makes some of the best quality
home gym equipment on the market
and that's no exception with these
dumbbells
thanks for watching everybody i hope
this video was really helpful and maybe
showed you guys some more of what these
dumbbells have to bring to the table
keep your eyes peeled for my next review
but in the meantime search bar bend
rogue hex dumbbell review and you can
read over everything we discuss here
today i'll catch y'all later
[Music]
you